Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department microfilmed entertainment contracts, 1924-1957 RL.11870
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Radio Contracts, 1927-1948; undated; 4
  - Lever Brothers--Lux Radio Theatre, 1936-1946; 131
    - Doris Dowling, 1945 Oct. 15 (Film-reel 402)
    - Dorothy Lamour, 1943 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 253)
    - Dorothy Lamour, 1944 Apr. 17 (Film-reel 401)
    - Dorothy Lamour, 1944 Oct. 9; 15 (Film-reel 402)
    - Dorothy McGuire, 1945 Sept. 3; Dec. 24 (Film-reel 402)
    - Dorothy Patrick, 1946 Apr. 1 (Film-reel 402)
    - Dorothy Porter, 1946 Nov. 25 (Film-reel 403)
    - Dragonwyck--Rights, 1946 Oct. 7 (Film-reel 403)
    - Each Dawn I Die--Consent, 1943 Mar. 11 (Film-reel 253)
    - Edgar Barrier, 1943 Sept. (Film-reel 253)
    - Edgar Barrier, 1944 Jan. 24-Sept. 4 (Film-reel 401)
    - Edgar Buchanan, 1943 Sept. 21 (Film-reel 253)
    - Edgar Buchanan, 1944 May 8 (Film-reel 401)
    - Edith Barrett, 1943 Sept. 7 (Film-reel 253)
    - Edith Head, 1945 Oct. 29 (Film-reel 402)
    - Edmund O'Brien, 1946 Mar. 4 (Film-reel 402)
    - Edna Best, 1943 Mar. 5; June 1 (Film-reel 253)
    - Edward G. Robinson, 1943 Jan. 22 (Film-reel 253)
    - Edward G. Robinson, 1944 Apr. 3 (Film-reel 401)
    - Edward G. Robinson, 1945 Apr. 16; June 25 (Film-reel 402)
    - Edward Ryan, 1944 Oct. 2 (Film-reel 401)
    - Eleanor Broder, 1945 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 402)
    - Eleanor Parker, 1945 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 402)
    - Elizabeth Patterson, 1945 May 7 (Film-reel 402)
    - Elizabeth Risdon, 1945 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 402)
    - Ella Raines, 1944 Mar. 27 (Film-reel 401)
    - Ella Raines, 1945 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 402)
    - Elsa Janssen, 1943 Sept. 27 (Film-reel 253)
    - Elsa Janssen, 1944 Feb. 7 (Film-reel 401)
    - Enchanted Cottage--Rights, 1945 Sept. 3 (Film-reel 402)
    - Ethel Barrymore, 1946 June 3 (Film-reel 402)
    - Eve Arden, 1943 Jan. 4 (Film-reel 253)
    - Eve Miller, 1946 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 403)
    - Evelyn Keyes, 1946 Apr. 15 (Film-reel 402)
    - Experiment Perilous--Rights, 1945 Sept. 10 (Film-reel 402)
    - Fallen Angel--Rights, 1946 June 17 (Film-reel 402)
    - Fallen Sparrow--Rights, 1944 Feb. 14 (Film-reel 401)
    - Farm paper ads, 1936-1938 (Film-reel 71)
    - Fay Bainter, 1943 Sept. 21 (Film-reel 253)
    - Five Graves to Cairo--Consent, 1943 Dec. 6 (Film-reel 253)
    - Flight for Freedom--Consent, 1943 May 8 (Film-reel 253)
    - Folios, 1944 Jan. 17 (Film-reel 401)
    - For Whom the Bell Tolls--Rights, 1945 Feb. 12 (Film-reel 402)
    - Fortunio Bonanova, 1943 Dec. 6 (Film-reel 253)
    - Frances Dee, 1944 Apr. 10 (Film-reel 401)
    - Frances Gifford, 1943 Dec. 20 (Film-reel 253)
    - Frances Gifford, 1945 Apr. 2-1946 Sept. 2 (Film-reel 402)
    - Frances Langford, 1945 Jan. 8 (Film-reel 402)
    - Franchot Tone, 1943 Mar. 15 (Film-reel 253)
    - Franchot Tone, 1943 Dec. 6 (Film-reel 253)
    - Franchot Tone, 1944 Mar. 20 (Film-reel 401)
    - Frank Craven, 1945 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 402)
    - Frank Morgan, 1944 Nov. 6; 1945 Mar. 12 (Film-reel 402)
    - Frank Sinatra, 1944 Feb. 21 (Film-reel 401)
    - Fred MacMurray, 1944 Oct. 30; 1946 May 13 (Film-reel 402)
    - From This Day Forward--Rights, 1946 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 403)
    - Gail Patrick, 1943 Jan. 25 (Film-reel 253)
    - Gail Patrick, 1946 Dec. 16 (Film-reel 403)
    - Gale Sondergaard, 1945 Feb. 12; Sept. 24 (Film-reel 402)
    - Gallant Journey--Rights, 1946 Nov. 11 (Film-reel 403)
    - Gary Cooper, 1943 Aug. 12 (Film-reel 253)
    - Gary Cooper, 1944 Oct. 23-1945 Feb. 12 (Film-reel 402)
    - Gaslight--Rights, 1946 Apr. 29 (Film-reel 402)
    - Gene Lockhart, 1943 Oct. 18 (Film-reel 253)
    - Gene Tierney, 1945 Feb. 5; 1946 Mar. 4 (Film-reel 402)
    - Gene Tierney, 1946 Oct. 7 (Film-reel 403)
    - George Brent, 1943 Feb. 16-Sept. 5 (Film-reel 253)
    - George Brent, 1945 Sept. 10; Oct. 29 (Film-reel 402)
    - George Burns, 1943 Feb. 1 (Film-reel 253)
    - George Coulouris, 1945 Jan. 15 (Film-reel 402)
    - George Murphy, 1943 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 253)
    - George Murphy, 1945 Oct. 22 (Film-reel 402)
    - George Raft, 1943 Mar. 10; June 26 (Film-reel 253)
    - George Raft, 1944 May 15 (Film-reel 401)
    - Ginger Rogers, 1943 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 253)
    - Ginger Rogers, 1945 Jan. 29 (Film-reel 402)
    - Ginny Simms, 1943 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 253)
    - Gladys O'Brien, 1945 Oct. 22; 1946 Sept. 2 (Film-reel 402)
    - Gladys O'Brien, 1946 Dec. 2 (Film-reel 403)
    - Glenn Ford, 1946 Nov. 11 (Film-reel 403)
    - Gloria Saunders, 1946 June 17 (Film-reel 402)
    - Gloria Tucker, 1946 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 402)
    - Gordon Oliver, 1945 Mar. 12 (Film-reel 402)
    - Government Girl--Rights, 1944 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 402)
    - Gracie Allen, 1943 Feb. 1 (Film-reel 253)
    - Greer Garson, 1943 Nov. 15 (Film-reel 253)
    - Greer Garson, 1944 Jan. 31 (Film-reel 401)
    - Greer Garson, 1945 Feb. 26-1946 Sept. 16 (Film-reel 402)
    - Greer Garson, 1946 Nov. 25 (Film-reel 403)
    - Gregory Peck, 1946 Jan. 14; Feb. 11 (Film-reel 402)
    - Grissley's Millions--Rights, 1945 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 402)
    - Guadalcanal Diary--Rights, 1944 Feb. 28 (Film-reel 401)
    - Guest in the House--Rights, 1945 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 402)
    - Guest Wife--Rights, 1945 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 402)
    - Hal Wallis, 1945 June 4; 18 (Film-reel 402)
    - Happy Land--Rights, 1944 Apr. 10 (Film-reel 401)
    - Harold Ober, 1946 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 402)
    - Harold Peary, 1943 Jan. 22 (Film-reel 253)
    - Harry Carey, 1943 July 5 (Film-reel 253)
    - Heather Angel, 1946 Mar. 18 (Film-reel 402)
    - Heaven Can Wait--Consent, 1943 Aug. 3; Oct. 1 (Film-reel 253)
    - Hedy Lamarr, 1944 Jan. 24 (Film-reel 401)
    - Helen Beverly, 1945 Jan. 15 (Film-reel 402)
    - Helen O'Hara, 1946 Jan. 14 (Film-reel 402)
    - Helen Rose, 1946 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 402)
    - Helene Stanley, 1946 Sept. 16 (Film-reel 402)
    - Hello, Frisco, Hello--Consent, 1943 Oct. 29 (Film-reel 253)
    - Herbert Marshall, 1943 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 253)
    - Herbert Marshall, 1944 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 401)
    - His Butler's Sister--Rights, 1944 Feb. 7 (Film-reel 401)
    - Hitler's Children--Consent, 1943 May 5 (Film-reel 253)
    - Home in Indiana--Rights, 1944 Oct. 2 (Film-reel 401)
    - Honky Tonk--Rights, 1946 Apr. 8 (Film-reel 402)
    - Hotel Imperial--Consent, 1943 Dec. 12 (Film-reel 253)
    - Humphrey Bogart, 1945 Apr. 30 (Film-reel 402)
    - Humphrey Bogart, 1946 Oct. 14 (Film-reel 403)
    - Hunt Stromberg, 1945 Sept. 3 (Film-reel 402)
    - I Never Left Home--Rights, 1945 Jan. 8 (Film-reel 402)
    - Ida Lupino, 1943 Apr. 21; July 7 (Film-reel 253)
    - Ida Lupino, 1945 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 402)
    - I'll Be Seeing You--Rights, 1945 Dec. 24 (Film-reel 402)
    - In Old Chicago--Rights, 1944 Oct. 9 (Film-reel 402)
    - In Old Oklahoma--Rights, 1944 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 401)
    - In Which We Serve--Consent, 1943 May 27 (Film-reel 253)
    - Ingrid Bergman, 1945 Feb. 12-1946 Apr. 29 (Film-reel 402)
    - Intermezzo--Rights, 1945 June 4 (Film-reel 402)
    - Irene Dunne, 1944 May 8 (Film-reel 401)
    - Irene Dunne, 1946 Dec. 9 (Film-reel 403)
    - Irving Pichell, 1945 June 11-Oct. 15 (Film-reel 402)
    - It Started with Eve--Rights, 1944 Nov. 20 (Film-reel 402)
    - It's a Date--Rights, 1945 Sept. 24 (Film-reel 402)
    - I've Always Loved You--Rights, 1946 Nov. 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - J. Carroll Naish, 1943 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 253)
    - J. Carroll Naish, 1944 Dec. 25; 1945 Oct. 15 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jack Benny, 1946 Dec. 16 (Film-reel 403)
    - Jack Carson, 1945 Oct. 8 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jacqueline White, 1946 Mar. 25 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jacqueline White, 1946 Dec. 30 (Film-reel 403)
    - James Cagney, 1945 Dec. 3 (Film-reel 402)
    - James Cardwell, 1945 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 402)
    - James Craig, 1944 June 19 (Film-reel 401)
    - James Craig, 1946 Sept. 2 (Film-reel 402)
    - James Dunn, 1945 May 7 (Film-reel 402)
    - James Gleason, 1944 Feb. 21 (Film-reel 401)
    - James Gleason, 1946 Dec. 16 (Film-reel 403)
    - James Stewart, 1945 Nov. 5; Dec. 17 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jane Eyre--Rights, 1944 June 5 (Film-reel 401)
    - Jane Glyde, 1945 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jane Nigh, 1945 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 402)
    - Janet Blair, 1943 June 22 (Film-reel 253)
    - Janet Blair, 1946 Nov. 11 (Film-reel 403)
    - Janet Thomas, 1946 Apr. 29 (Film-reel 402)
    - Janis Carter, 1946 Nov. 11 (Film-reel 403)
    - Jean Arthur, 1943 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 253)
    - Jean Aumont, 1943 Mar. 22 (Film-reel 253)
    - Jean Bartell, 1944 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 401)
    - Jean Crain, 1946 June 24 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jean Hershelt, 1944 Oct. 16 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jeanette MacDonald, 1944 June 12; Sept. 4 (Film-reel 401)
    - Jeanne Crain, 1944 Oct. 2 (Film-reel 401)
    - Jeff Donnell, 1946 May 13 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jeff Donnell, 1946 Dec. 9 (Film-reel 403)
    - Jennifer Jones, 1944 Oct. 16 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jerome Courtland, 1946 Dec. 9 (Film-reel 403)
    - Jerry Colonna, 1945 Jan. 8 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jesse L. Lasky, 1945 Feb. 19 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jessica Tandy, 1946 Mar. 11 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jimmy Durante, 1946 May 27 (Film-reel 402)
    - Joan Bennett, 1942 Dec. 30; 1943 Apr. 20 (Film-reel 253)
    - Joan Bennett, 1944 Dec. 11; 1945 June 25 (Film-reel 402)
    - Joan Blondell, 1943 Jan. 12 (Film-reel 253)
    - Joan Blondell, 1945 Nov. 5; 1946 May 20 (Film-reel 402)
    - Joan Caulfield, 1945 May 7 (Film-reel 402)
    - Joan Caulfield, 1946 Oct. 21 (Film-reel 403)
    - Joan Fontaine, 1945 Oct. 29 (Film-reel 402)
    - Joan Fontaine, 1946 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 403)
    - Joan Winfield, 1946 Dec. 16 (Film-reel 403)
    - Joe Cotton, 1943 June 16 (Film-reel 253)
    - John Carradine, 1943 Mar. 4 (Film-reel 253)
    - John Cromwell, 1945 Aug. 27 (Film-reel 402)
    - John Garfield, 1945 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 402)
    - John Hodiak, 1944 Oct. 9-1946 Apr. 8 (Film-reel 402)
    - John Loder, 1944 Jan. 24 (Film-reel 401)
    - John Lund, 1946 June 10 (Film-reel 402)
    - John Payne, 1946 Sept. 23 (Film-reel 402)
    - Johnny Eagaer--Rights, 1946 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 402)
    - Jose Iturbi, 1946 May 27 (Film-reel 402)
    - Joseph Cotten, 1944 May 8 (Film-reel 401)
    - Joseph Cotten, 1945 Dec. 24; 1946 Apr. 22 (Film-reel 402)
    - Joseph Cotten, 1946 Nov. 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - Joseph Cotton, 1945 June 4 (Film-reel 402)
    - Joyce Elaine Mackenzie, 1945 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 402)
    - Judy Garland, 1946 Jan. 28 (Film-reel 402)
    - Judy Garland, 1946 Dec. 2 (Film-reel 403)
    - Julie Bishop, 1944 May 15 (Film-reel 401)
    - June Allyson, 1946 Mar. 11 (Film-reel 402)
    - June Duprez, 1945 Jan. 22-1946 June 3 (Film-reel 402)
    - June Haver, 1944 Oct. 2 (Film-reel 401)
    - Katherine Connors, 1945 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 402)
    - Kathleen--Consent, 1943 Dec. 21; 1944 Feb. 29 (Film-reel 253)
    - Kathryn Grayson, 1944 Dec. 25 (Film-reel 402)
    - Kay Christopher, 1946 Aug. 26 (Film-reel 402)
    - Kay Francis, 1943 Feb. 16 (Film-reel 253)
    - Keenan Wynn, 1944 June 19 (Film-reel 401)
    - Kent Smith, 1943 May 6 (Film-reel 253)
    - Kentucky--Rights, 1945 May 28 (Film-reel 402)
    - Keye Luke, 1943 Nov. 5 (Film-reel 253)
    - Keys of the Kingdom--Rights, 1945 Nov. 19 (Film-reel 402)
    - Ladies in Retirement--Consent, 1943 Apr. 30 (Film-reel 253)
    - Ladies in Retirement--Consent, 1943 Sept. 24 (Film-reel 253)
    - Lady in the Dark--Rights, 1945 Jan. 29 (Film-reel 402)
    - Laird Cregar, 1943 Jan. 13-Apr. 9 (Film-reel 253)
    - Lana Turner, 1943 Mar. 22; Oct. 18 (Film-reel 253)
    - Lana Turner, 1946 Apr. 8 (Film-reel 402)
    - Laraine Day, 1943 Sept. 24 (Film-reel 253)
    - Laraine Day, 1944 Dec. 4-1945 May 28 (Film-reel 402)
    - Laura--Rights, 1945 Feb. 5 (Film-reel 402)
    - Lauren Bacall, 1946 Oct. 14 (Film-reel 403)
    - Laverne Stiffler, 1946 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 402)
    - Les Tremayne, 1943 Oct. 25 (Film-reel 253)
    - Letter to Russell Birdwell regarding Jane Russell commercial of Nov. 12, 1945 Nov. 9 (Film-reel 402)
    - Libel--Consent, 1943 Mar. 5 (Film-reel 253)
    - Lina Romay, 1946 Feb. 18 (Film-reel 402)
    - Linda Christian, 1946 Sept. 2 (Film-reel 402)
    - Linda Darnell, 1944 June 26 (Film-reel 401)
    - Linda Darnell, 1945 Mar. 12; 1946 June 17 (Film-reel 402)
    - Lionel Barrymore, 1944 June 26 (Film-reel 401)
    - Lionel Barrymore, 1945 Jan. 29-1946 Feb. 18 (Film-reel 402)
    - Lizabeth Scott, 1946 Jan. 7 (Film-reel 402)
    - Lloyd Nolan, 1944 Feb. 28 (Film-reel 401)
    - Lola Deem, 1946 Dec. 2 (Film-reel 403)
    - Loretta Young, 1943 May 26; Nov. 9 (Film-reel 253)
    - Loretta Young, 1944 June 5 (Film-reel 401)
    - Loretta Young, 1945 May 21-1946 Sept. 9 (Film-reel 402)
    - Lost Angel--Rights, 1944 June 19 (Film-reel 401)
    - Lost Angel--Rights, 1945 Oct. 29 (Film-reel 402)
    - Love Letters--Rights, 1946 Apr. 22 (Film-reel 402)
    - Lucille Ball, 1944 Sept. 25 (Film-reel 401)
    - Lucille Barkely, 1946 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 403)
    - Lucky Partners--Rights, 1944 Sept. 25 (Film-reel 401)
    - Lux for Dishes-Hands, 1937-1938 (Film-reel 71)
    - Lydia Schiller, 1946 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 402)
    - Lynn Bari, 1945 Mar. 19; 1946 Sept. 23 (Film-reel 402)
    - Lynn Bari, 1946 Dec. 30 (Film-reel 403)
    - Madame Curie--Rights, 1946 Sept. 16 (Film-reel 402)
    - Made for Each Other--Rights, 1945 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 402)
    - Magnificent Obsession--Rights, 1944 Nov. 13 (Film-reel 402)
    - Margaret and Gladys O'Brien--block contract of May 5, 1946 Feb. 18 (Film-reel 402)
    - Margaret O'Brien, 1944 June 19 (Film-reel 401)
    - Margaret O'Brien, 1944 Nov. 6-1946 Sept. 2 (Film-reel 402)
    - Margaret O'Brien, 1946 Dec. 2 (Film-reel 403)
    - Margot Woode, 1946 June 10 (Film-reel 402)
    - Marguerite Chapman, 1944 Apr. 3 (Film-reel 401)
    - Marguerite Chapman, 1946 May 13 (Film-reel 402)
    - Marilyn Maxwell, 1944 Feb. 21 (Film-reel 401)
    - Marissa O'Brien, 1945 Oct. 22-1946 Sept. 2 (Film-reel 402)
    - Marjorie Main, 1946 Apr. 1 (Film-reel 402)
    - Marjorie Rambeau, Bill Woolfenden, 1942 June 10; 1943 Jan. 13 (Film-reel 253)
    - Marjorie Reynolds, 1945 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 402)
    - Marjorie Riordan, 1945 Oct. 1 (Film-reel 402)
    - Mark Hellinger, 1945 Apr. 30-Sept. 10 (Film-reel 402)
    - Mark Stevens, 1946 June 17 (Film-reel 402)
    - Mark Stevens, 1946 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 403)
    - Marsha Hunt, 1944 June 19 (Film-reel 401)
    - Marsha Hunt, 1945 Jan. 1; Dec. 17 (Film-reel 402)
    - Martha Hyer, 1946 May 20 (Film-reel 402)
    - Martha Scott, 1944 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 401)
    - Mary Martin, 1943 Jan. 8 (Film-reel 253)
    - Mary Stuart, 1946 May 27 (Film-reel 402)
    - Maureen O'Hara, 1943 Oct. 4 (Film-reel 253)
    - Maureen O'Hara, 1944 Feb. 14 (Film-reel 401)
    - Maureen O'Hara, 1946 June 17 (Film-reel 402)
    - Maureen O'Hara, 1946 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 403)
    - Maureen O'Sullivan, 1944 Jan. 10; Apr. 24 (Film-reel 401)
    - Maureen O'Sullivan, 1944 Dec. 18 (Film-reel 402)
    - Maytime--Rights, 1944 Sept. 4 (Film-reel 401)
    - Meet Me in St. Louis--Rights, 1946 Dec. 2 (Film-reel 403)
    - Merle Oberon, 1944 Nov. 27 (Film-reel 402)
    - Meta Carpenter, 1946 Oct. 7 (Film-reel 403)
    - Mike Mezurki, 1945 June 11 (Film-reel 402)
    - Mikhail Rasumny, 1945 Feb. 12; Oct. 15 (Film-reel 402)
    - Miriam Hopkins, 1944 Mar. 20; May 29 (Film-reel 401)
    - Miss Susie Slagles--Rights, 1946 Oct. 21 (Film-reel 403)
    - Mitchell Leisen, 1945 May 7-Oct. 29 (Film-reel 402)
    - Moontide--Rights, 1945 Apr. 30 (Film-reel 402)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Cugat--Consent, 1943 Jan. 29; Feb. 2 (Film-reel 253)
    - Mr. Lucky--Consent, 1943 May 5 (Film-reel 253)
    - Mr. Skeffington--Rights, 1945 Oct. 1 (Film-reel 402)
    - Mrs. Miniver--Consent, 1943 Sept. 3-1944 Feb. 28 (Film-reel 253)
    - Mrs. Parkington--Rights, 1946 Nov. 25 (Film-reel 403)
    - Murder My Sweet--Rights, 1945 June 11 (Film-reel 402)
    - Music for Millions--Rights, 1946 May 27 (Film-reel 402)
    - Music releases, 1944-1945 (Film-reel 402)
    - My Friend Flicka--Consent, 1943 Apr. 30 (Film-reel 253)
    - My Gal Sal--Consent, 1943 Jan. 11 (Film-reel 253)
    - My Sister Eileen--Consent, 1943 June 23 (Film-reel 253)
    - Myrna Dell, 1946 June 3 (Film-reel 402)
    - Nan Leslie, 1946 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 403)
    - Nancy Gates, 1945 Jan. 15; Nov. 5 (Film-reel 402)
    - Natalie Wood, 1946 May 6 (Film-reel 402)
    - Naughty Marietta--Rights, 1944 June 12 (Film-reel 401)
    - Nelson Eddy, 1943 Sept. 3 (Film-reel 253)
    - Nelson Eddy, 1944 June 12; Sept. 4 (Film-reel 401)
    - Next Time We Love--Consent, 1938 Nov. 7 (Film-reel 254)
    - Nina Foch, 1946 Apr. 8 (Film-reel 402)
    - Nina Foch, 1946 Oct. 21 (Film-reel 403)
    - None But the Lonely--Rights, 1946 June 3 (Film-reel 402)
    - Now Voyager--Consent, 1943 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 253)
    - Now Voyager--Rights, 1946 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 402)
    - O.S.S.--Rights, 1946 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 403)
    - Old Acquaintance--Rights, 1944 May 29 (Film-reel 401)
    - Olga San Juan, 1946 Nov. 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - Olivia de Havilland, 1944 May 1; Sept. 18 (Film-reel 401)
    - Olivia de Havilland, 1945 Jan. 22-1946 June 10 (Film-reel 402)
    - Once Upon a Honeymoon--Consent, 1943 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 253)
    - Only Yesterday--Rights, 1945 Apr. 16 (Film-reel 402)
    - Orson Welles, 1944 June 5; Sept. 11 (Film-reel 401)
    - Orson Welles, 1945 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 402)
    - Otto Kruger, 1943 Mar. 1; May 6 (Film-reel 253)
    - Otto Kruger, 1944 May 29 (Film-reel 401)
    - Otto Kruger, 1945 Feb. 5-Mar. 19 (Film-reel 402)
    - Otto Kruger, 1946 Nov. 4 (Film-reel 403)
    - Otto Preminger, 1943 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 253)
    - Our Vines Have Tender Grapes--Rights, 1946 Sept. 2 (Film-reel 402)
    - Pardon My Past--Rights, 1946 May 13 (Film-reel 402)
    - Pat O'Brien, 1943 Apr. 20; Oct. 12 (Film-reel 253)
    - Pat O'Brien, 1944 Feb. 7 (Film-reel 401)
    - Pat O'Brien, 1945 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 402)
    - Pat O'Brien, 1946 Dec. 30 (Film-reel 403)
    - Pat O'Malley, 1943 June 15 (Film-reel 253)
    - Paul Guilfoyle, 1945 Jan. 15 (Film-reel 402)
    - Paul Henreid, 1943 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 253)
    - Paul Henreid, 1945 Sept. 10; Oct. 1 (Film-reel 402)
    - Paul Lucas, 1944 May 1 (Film-reel 401)
    - Paul Luke, 1946 May 20 (Film-reel 402)
    - Paulette Goddard, 1943 Jan. 6; Aug. 5; Oct. 8 (Film-reel 253)
    - Paulette Goddard, 1944 Oct. 30; 1946 Mar. 18 (Film-reel 402)
    - Penny Serenade--Rights, 1944 May 8 (Film-reel 401)
    - Penny Serenade--Rights, 1946 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 402)
    - Phantom of the Opera--Consent, 1943 Sept. 9 (Film-reel 253)
    - Philip Ahn, 1943 Nov. 17 (Film-reel 253)
    - Pied Piper--Rights, 1944 Nov. 6 (Film-reel 402)
    - Practically Yours--Rights, 1945 Aug. 27 (Film-reel 402)
    - Presenting Lily Mars--Rights, 1946 Mar. 11 (Film-reel 402)
    - Preston Foster, 1943 Jan. 4 (Film-reel 253)
    - Preston Foster, 1944 Feb. 28 (Film-reel 401)
    - Preston Foster, 1944 Nov. 27; 1946 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 402)
    - Preston Sturges, 1945 May 21 (Film-reel 402)
    - Pride of the Marines--Rights, 1945 Dec. 31 (Film-reel 402)
    - Pride of the Yankees--Consent, 1943 Aug. 24 (Film-reel 253)
    - Proudly We Hail--Consent, 1943 Oct. 26 (Film-reel 253)
    - Random Harvest--Rights, 1944 Jan. 31 (Film-reel 401)
    - Ray Milland, 1943 Feb. 15; Apr. 19 (Film-reel 253)
    - Ray Milland, 1945 Jan. 29; Aug. 27 (Film-reel 402)
    - Raymond Massey, 1944 May 15 (Film-reel 401)
    - Raymond Walburn, 1944 June 26 (Film-reel 401)
    - Reap the Wild Wind--Consent, 1943 Feb. 18 (Film-reel 253)
    - Reed Radley, 1944 Oct. 23 (Film-reel 402)
    - Release--Carol Anderson, 1945 Nov. 8 (Film-reel 402)
    - Release--Jerry Woods, 1945 Nov. 2 (Film-reel 402)
    - Release--Joan Bennett, 1945 Dec. 10 (Film-reel 402)
    - Release--Leslie Charteris, 1945 Dec. 27 (Film-reel 402)
    - Release--Louise Randall Pearson, 1945 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 402)
    - Releases--Joan Bennett, Sorenson, Charteris, Mitch Leisen, 1945 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 402)
    - Release--Xavier Cugat, 1945 Oct. 22 (Film-reel 402)
    - Renee Randall, 1946 Sept. 9 (Film-reel 402)
    - Revision of commercial in letter to Margaret O'Donnell, 1945 Nov. 8 (Film-reel 402)
    - Richard Jaeckel, 1944 Feb. 28 (Film-reel 401)
    - Richard Llewellyn, 1946 June 3 (Film-reel 402)
    - Richard Long, 1946 May 6 (Film-reel 402)
    - Rita Corday, 1945 Sept. 3 (Film-reel 402)
    - Rita Hayworth, 1943 Apr. 19 (Film-reel 253)
    - Rita Hayworth, 1944 Sept. 11 (Film-reel 401)
    - Rita Hayworth, 1946 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 402)
    - Rita Johnson, 1943 May 24 (Film-reel 253)
    - Rita Johnson, 1946 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 402)
    - Road to Morocco--Consent, 1943 Mar. 23 (Film-reel 253)
    - Robert Cummings, 1946 Aug. 26 (Film-reel 402)
    - Robert Montgomery, 1944 Dec. 4 (Film-reel 402)
    - Robert Paige, 1944 Feb. 7 (Film-reel 401)
    - Robert Taylor, 1943 May 25 (Film-reel 253)
    - Robert Taylor, 1946 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 402)
    - Robert Young, 1943 Apr. 15-Nov. 5 (Film-reel 253)
    - Robert Young, 1944 Feb. 14 (Film-reel 401)
    - Robert Young, 1944 Oct. 9-1945 Nov. 12 (Film-reel 402)
    - Roberta Jonay, 1946 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 402)
    - Roddy McDowell, 1946 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 402)
    - Roderick (Roddy) McDowell, 1943 June 1 (Film-reel 253)
    - Roland Young, 1944 Dec. 4 (Film-reel 402)
    - Ronald Colman, 1943 Mar. 2-May 20 (Film-reel 253)
    - Ronald Colman, 1944 Jan. 31 (Film-reel 401)
    - Ronald Colman, 1944 Dec. 18-1946 Mar. 18 (Film-reel 402)
    - Rosalind Ivan, 1945 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 402)
    - Rosalind Russell, 1943 June 2; 24 (Film-reel 253)
    - Rosalind Russell, 1945 Oct. 8 (Film-reel 402)
    - Rosemary DeCamp, 1945 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 402)
    - Roughly Speaking--Rights, 1945 Oct. 8 (Film-reel 402)
    - Roy Rogers, 1944 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 401)
    - Ruth Brady, 1946 Jan. 28 (Film-reel 402)
    - Ruth Hussey, 1943 May 3 (Film-reel 253)
    - Ruth Warrick, 1943 Oct. 25 (Film-reel 253)
    - Salty O'Rourke--Rights, 1945 Nov. 26 (Film-reel 402)
    - Salute to the Marines--Consent, 1943 Sept. 22-1944 Feb. 28 (Film-reel 253)
    - Sentimental Journey--Rights, 1946 Sept. 23 (Film-reel 402)
    - Seventh Heaven--Rights, 1944 Oct. 16 (Film-reel 402)
    - Shadow of a Doubt--Rights, 1944 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 401)
    - She Knew All the Answers--Consent, 1943 Jan. 4 (Film-reel 253)
    - Sherry Berger, 1945 Dec. 3 (Film-reel 402)
    - Shirley Temple, 1943 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 253)
    - Signe Hasso, 1944 Nov. 6 (Film-reel 402)
    - Sing You Sinners--Rights, 1945 May 7 (Film-reel 402)
    - Slightly Dangerous--Consent, 1943 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 253)
    - Sonny Tufts, 1943 Aug. 31; Oct. 8 (Film-reel 253)
    - Springtime in the Rockies--Rights, 1944 May 22 (Film-reel 401)
    - Standing Room Only--Rights, 1944 Oct. 30 (Film-reel 402)
    - Stanley Hodges, 1945 Jan. 15 (Film-reel 402)
    - State Fair--Rights, 1946 June 24 (Film-reel 402)
    - Stocking ads, 1937-1938 (Film-reel 71)
    - Sue England, 1946 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 402)
    - Sunday Dinner for a Soldier--Rights, 1945 Feb. 19 (Film-reel 402)
    - Susan Hayward, 1945 Apr. 23 (Film-reel 402)
    - Susan Peters, 1943 Dec. 2 (Film-reel 253)
    - Susan Peters, 1946 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 402)
    - Susanna Foster, 1943 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 253)
    - Susanna Foster, 1944 Nov. 20 (Film-reel 402)
    - Suspicion--Rights, 1944 Sept. 18 (Film-reel 401)
    - Swanee River--Rights, 1945 Apr. 2 (Film-reel 402)
    - Sylvia Sidney, 1945 Dec. 3 (Film-reel 402)
    - Take It Easy--Rights, 1944 May 8 (Film-reel 401)
    - Talk of the Town--Consent, 1943 Apr. 30 (Film-reel 253)
    - Teletype--Luke and Jerry Woods, 1945 Nov. 2 (Film-reel 402)
    - Teletype--Mrs. Sorenson, 1945 Dec. 20 (Film-reel 402)
    - Teletype--Veronica Lake, revision of commercial, 1945 Oct. 26 (Film-reel 402)
    - Tender Comrade--Rights, 1944 May 2; 1945 Jan. 22 (Film-reel 402)